getrocketbook.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Rocketbook

* **Introduction** Thank you for visiting Rocketbook and, if applicable, downloading our App. Rocketbook respects the privacy of its Users and has developed this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Policy describes the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

We encourage you to read this Policy carefully before using our App and Websites, or otherwise providing Personal Information to us.

Please read our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy carefully, as you must agree to both documents in order to be permitted to use our Service. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT AND AGREE WITH OUR POLICY THEN PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US..

  2. **Definitions**

Throughout this Policy, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them. The following is a non-exhaustive list of definitions of words and phrases found in this document:

“App” refers to our mobile software application;

“Personal Information” means any personal information that may identify You, such as your name, email address, geographical address, and telephone number.

“Product” means any of the Rocketbook products we offer for sale from time to time;

“Rocketbook,” “we,” and “us” refers to our company, known as “Rocket Innovations, Inc.”; our Site; our Service; our App; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context in which the word is used;

“Service” refers to the services that we provide, including our Site and our App;

“Site” refers to our websites, getrocketbook.com;

“User” refers to anyone who uses our Service;

“you” refers to you, the person who is governed by this Privacy Policy.

  3. **Information Collected**

_Information provided by you_

We collect Personal Information from you when you:

  * download our App and sign up for our Service;
  * purchase Products from us;
  * make an inquiry, provide feedback, or otherwise contact us by post, email or on our website, including through the Contact Us Page;
  * complete any of the webforms on the Website;
  * participate in any survey, unless you respond anonymously.

All personal data that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate. We may keep a record of any conversation that we have. If you provide us with inaccurate or false data, and we suspect or identify fraud, we will record this. In addition we may search at fraud prevention agencies for information on you as part of our due diligence to ensure we comply with anti-money laundering legislation.

When you sign up to our Service, you will provide us with certain information:

  * Essential information: When you register a Rocketbook account, you will need to provide your email address and choose a password.
  * Non-essential information: Your username if you wish to provide it.
  * Information from correspondence: You will provide certain personal data if you contact us by email, use any of the webforms on the Website, or contact us by mail, fax or other offline means.
  * Survey information: If you participate in any survey, you will provide certain personal data as part of your response, unless you respond anonymously.

_Information we collect automatically_

There is certain information that we collect automatically as the result of your use of the Service. This information includes but is not limited to:

  * The Internet Protocol (IP) address of the device from which you access the service (this can sometimes be used to derive the country or city from which you are accessing the service)
  * The site that you visited immediately prior to visiting the Website
  * The specific actions that you take on the Service, including the pages and screens that you view or visit
  * Any search terms that you may enter on the Service
  * The time, frequency and duration of your visits to the Service
  * Your browser type and operating system
  * The nature of the device from which you are accessing the Service, for example, whether you are accessing the Platform from a computer or from a mobile device and its device-ID
  * Your location data (e.g. IP Address)
  * Information collected through cookies and similar technology, as described in our Cookies Policy
  * Information regarding your interaction with email messages, for example, whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded the email message

Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

_Information We Receive or Collect When You Access the Site or Applications on a Mobile Device_

When you use our Service, we receive information generated through the use of the Service, either entered by you or others who use the Service with you, or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, duration of session, connection information, etc.). We may also collect usage and log data about how the Service is accessed and used, including information about the device you are using the Service on, IP addresses, location information, language settings, what operating system you are using, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data to help us support the Service. For certain optional app features utilizing Handwriting Recognition OCR including Smart Search and Email Transcription only, read access and storage of scanned content on a reputable cloud storage provider is necessary to provide the feature’s functionality. You may disable these features at any time.

_Your Choices About Collection and Use of Your Information_

You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of our Service because such Personal Information may be required in order for you to register as a User; ask a question; or initiate other transactions.

  4. **Use of Your Information**

In general, we collect, store and use your information to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. One important use of your information is communication. We may use information collected from you, including in any one or more of the following ways:

  * Create and administer your account
  * Manage your order for our Products and deal with any returns or refunds
  * Provide you with technical support
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send you Product updates, marketing communication, and service information
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Enhance or improve user experience, our Site, or our Service
  * Send emails about our Site, this Policy, or respond to inquiries
  * Send emails about service updates and notifications regarding your account, and (if you have elected to receive them using your account preferences) newsletters, marketing messages, and certain email notifications.
  * Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service
  * Research and analytics purposes
  * Compliance with policies, procedures, and laws

Please note you can unsubscribe from any Rocketbook email list anytime or modify the type of emails you would like to receive from us. You may also request that we delete your account and remove all your data by sending an email to[remove@getrocketbook.com](mailto:remove@getrocketbook.com).

We may send promotional email messages ("Promotional Communications") directly or in partnership with parties other than Rocketbook. Each Promotional Communication will generally offer recipients choices about receiving additional messages. We may also send push notifications to your mobile device to provide App updates and other relevant messages, which you manage in our Service. You may be able to manage them from your device’s settings page for the relevant service.

_Mobile Analytics_

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your device. This software may record information such as how often you use the App, the events that occur within the App, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the App was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any Personal Information you submit within the mobile App. However, information on individual usage of the Service, including, but not limited to, individual IP addresses, may be analyzed on a case-specific basis to resolve a technical difficulty or to assist in resolving or investigating any misuse of the Service.

_Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information_

Users may in some cases be able to review, edit, and delete the Personal Information they have provided to us by logging into their account on the App and editing their account or contacting[remove@getrocketbook.com](mailto:remove@getrocketbook.com) to have your data removed and your account deleted from our systems. If you ask us to delete your account, we will do so within a reasonable period of time. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such.

  5. **Cookies**

We use cookies to remember your preferences. For this reason, it is necessary that you enable cookies in your browser, and you hereby acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system.

  6. **Third Party Websites**

Rocketbook may post links to third-party websites on its Site. These third-party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by Rocketbook, and we are not liable for the conduct of these third-party websites.

Please be aware that this Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any Personal Information relating to members of the Service or Site. Rocketbook bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third-party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.

  7. **Third Party Access to Your Information**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with Rocketbook to disclose your Personal Information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.  
  
For our legitimate business interests, we use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.  We shall ask and require these third parties to implement appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect against unauthorized disclosure of personal data, and only to process personal data in accordance with our instructions and applicable laws, and to the extent necessary to provide their services to us.

  8. **International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to—and maintained on—computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Rocketbook transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Policy followed by your submission of such Personal Information represents your agreement to that transfer.

We also may use certain reputable third parties, some of whom may be located outside of the European Economic Area, to provide us with certain specialized services related to the Platform. These third parties will have access to certain information about you, but only where this is necessary in order for those third parties to provide their services to us. Where we transfer personal data to these third parties, we ask and require these third parties to implement appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect against unauthorized disclosure of personal data, and only to process personal data in accordance with our instructions and to the extent necessary to provide their services to us.

We are dedicated to protecting the privacy of your Personal Information when working with third parties. It is our policy to request that our third-party providers sign a written agreement confirming that they will use Personal Information or other information we share with them solely for the purpose to assist us and not for anything outside the scope of the services they are providing to us. While we may not always be successful in obtaining such an agreement for various reasons, we nevertheless attempt to facilitate access only to those third-party providers that share our respect for your privacy and adhere to privacy and security obligations in a manner consistent with our own policies and/or commercially reasonable practices; however, we cannot take responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of those third-party providers.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you authorize us to collect, share, store, and otherwise use your information from time to time in conjunction with various applications and solutions that enable us to better manage our communications with you and improve the Service.

  9. **Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes**

At times, it may become necessary for legal purposes, to release your information in response to a request from a government agency or a private litigant. You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is necessary to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena or other order affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena or order, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you, and release your information to, third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.

  10. **Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications**

We shall process your Personal Information in a manner that ensures appropriate security of your Personal Information, including protection against unauthorized or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage, using appropriate technical or organisational measures.  

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, including using SSL certificates. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your Personal Information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

  11. **Security Measures**

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, including using SSL certificates. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

  12. **Children’s Rights/General Audience Website**

Our Service is general audience services and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information as defined in the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") from children under the age of 13. In order to create an account on our Service, we do require that all users provide an email address and create a password. If you are a child under thirteen (13) years of age, you are not permitted to send any information about yourself to us through the Service. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from any person under the age of 13.

In the event that we become aware that we have inadvertently received Personal Information from any child, we will dispose of that information or otherwise treat it in accordance with COPPA and other applicable laws and regulations. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of thirteen (13) has provided us with Personal Information without COPPA-required consent, please contact us at:[legal@getrocketbook.com](mailto:legal@getrocketbook.com).

_Web Purchases._

Although Rocketbook may sell and promote children's products in some instances, all of our products are intended to be purchased only by adults. If you are under 18 years old and you want to buy something through the Service, you must have an adult buy it for you.

_California Children’s Privacy Rights_

If you are under the age of 18, or the parent of a user under the age of 18, residing in California, you are entitled to request removal of content or Personal Information you have posted on our Properties. If you would like to request removal of your or your child’s content or Personal Information, please email us at[remove@getrocketbook.com](mailto:remove@getrocketbook.com) for assistance, or you can delete specific information (or delete your or your child’s account) directly. Please keep in mind that deletion or removal of content or account may require us to terminate the account in question and we reserve the right to prohibit further use of our Service. Please note that removal of your content or Personal Information does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal, as there may be deidentified or recoverable elements of your content or Personal Information on our servers in some form. Additionally, we will not remove content or Personal Information that we may be required to retain under applicable federal and state laws.

  13. **Your California Privacy Rights**

Rocketbook permits residents of California to use its services. Therefore, it is the intent of Rocketbook to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain Personal Information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at[legal@getrocketbook.com](mailto:legal@getrocketbook.com) with any questions.

  14. **Sale or Merger**

In the event that Rocketbook undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, for our legitimate interests we may share all of your information, including Personal Information, to any interested buyer and the successor organization in such transition. If material changes to Rocketbook's privacy practices are known by us to occur as a result of the business transition, we will notify you and other users of the business transition prior to transferring your Personal Information. We may otherwise disclose your information in connection with such business transition.

  15. **Your Rights**

You have a number of rights under applicable laws. You may in some cases be able to exercise these rights yourself, such as the rights to review, edit, and delete the Personal Information you have provided to us by logging into your account on the App and editing your account accordingly. Otherwise, you should contact[legal@getrocketbook.com](mailto:legal@getrocketbook.com) to exercise your rights. Please note that we reserve the right to charge an administrative fee if your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive.  

You can also require us to correct errors in the Personal Information that we process for you if it is inaccurate, incomplete, or out of date.  

You also have the right at any time to require that we delete your Personal Information that we hold for you. If you ask us to delete your Personal Information we will do so within a reasonable period of time.

At any time, you can withdraw your consent to receive our marketing emails.

  16. **Retention of Personal Information**

We retain your personal data in accordance with applicable laws. The length of time we keep your personal data depends on what it is and whether we have an on-going business need to retain it (for example if you have an account with us or to comply with applicable legal, tax or accounting requirements). Once we no longer have an on-going business need to retain your personal data, we shall make sure it is deleted or made it anonymous within our systems.  

  17. **Amendments**

We may amend this Policy from time to time. When we amend this Policy, we will post the amended version on this page. You must read this page each time that you use our Service, and your continued use of our Service shall constitute your acceptance of any such amendments. Changes to this Policy take effect from the date of publication.

Last Modified: June 24, 2019

Copyright © 2019 Rocketbook, All Rights Reserved
